/*creating an array and passing the number,question,options and answers*/
let questions=[
	{
		numb:1,
		question:" Which of the following is generally used for performing tasks like creating the structure of the relations, deleting relation?",
		answer:"DDL(Data Definition Language)",
		options:[
			"DML(Data Manipulation Language)",
			"Query",
			"Relational Schema",
			"DDL(Data Definition Language)"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:2,
		question:"Which of the following provides the ability to query information from the database and insert tuples into, delete tuples from, and modify tuples in the database?",
		answer:"DML(Data Manipulation Language)",
		options:[
			"DML(Data Manipulation Language)",
			"DDL(Data Definition Language)",
			"Query",
			"Relational Schema"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:3,
		question:"Which one of the following given statements possibly contains the error?",
		answer:"select empid where empid = 1009 and Lastname = 'GELLER';",
		options:[
			"select * from emp where empid = 10003;",
			"select empid from emp where empid = 10006;",
			"select empid from emp;",
			"select empid where empid = 1009 and Lastname = 'GELLER';"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:4,
		question:"What do you mean by one to many relationships?",
		answer:"One teacher can have many classes",
		options:[
			"One class may have many teachers",
			"One teacher can have many classes",
			"Many classes may have many teachers",
			"Many teachers may have many classes"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:5,
		question:"The term 'NTFS' refers to which one of the following?",
		answer:"New Technology File System",
		options:[
			"New Technology File System",
			"New Tree File System",
			"New Table type File System",
			"Both A and C"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:6,
		question:"The term 'FAT' is stands for_____",
		answer:"File Allocation Table",
		options:[
			"File Allocation Tree",
			"File Allocation Table",
			"File Allocation Graph",
			"All of the above"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:7,
		question:"Which one of the following refers to the 'data about data'?",
		answer:"Meta Data",
		options:[
			"Directory",
			"Sub Data",
			"Warehouse",
			"Meta Data"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:8,
		question:"To which of the following the term 'DBA' referred?",
		answer:"Database Administrator",
		options:[
			"Data Bank Administrator",
			"Database Administrator",
			"Data Administrator",
			"None of the above"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:9,
		question:"Rows of a relation are known as the _______.",
		answer:"All of the above",
		options:[
			"Degree",
			"Tuples",
			"Entity",
			"All of the above"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:10,
		question:"Which one of the following is a type of Data Manipulation Command?",
		answer:"Delete",
		options:[
			"Create",
			"Alter",
			"Delete",
			"All of the above"
		]
	},
];